Guide to the Robin Winks, Buildings and Grounds Committee, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Robin Winks, Buildings and Grounds Committee, Yale University, records
1980-1984
RU 524
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
0.75
(2 boxes)
The records consist of agenda, memoranda, and reports kept by Professor Robin Winks while a member of the Buildings and Grounds committee.
Yale University. Buildings and Grounds Committee
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 6 (YRG 6), Records of Yale committees.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the records is restricted. See Collection Contents for details.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of agenda, memoranda, and reports kept by Professor Robin Winks while a member of the Buildings and Grounds committee.
Arrangement
The records are arranged chronologically.
College buildings; Winks, Robin W., 1930-; Yale University -- Administration; Yale University -- Buildings; Yale University. Buildings and Grounds Committee
- Records of Robin Winks, 1980-1984; Accession 1987-A-095
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2020.
  Scope and Contents
  Records kept by Robin Winks while a member of the Buildings and Grounds Committee. Includes agenda, memos, and reports.
  - 1980 May 19 - 1981 August (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 1981 September 3 - December 22 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 1982 January 4 - February 25 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - 1982 March 5 - April 22 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - 1982 May (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - 1982 January 1 - August 10 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - 1982 September (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - 1982 October 14 - November 18 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - 1982 December 2 - 1983 February 24 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - 1983 March 10 - August 18 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - 1983 September 9 - December 15 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - 1984 January 4 - April 26 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - 1984 May 10 - July 12 (Box 2, Folder 13)